# Arman Nikkhah Dehnavi

Data analyst in building science

 $R^{G}$ 

in



## **EDUCATION** -

## MASTER OF SCIENCE-BUILDING SCIENCE

Shahid beheshti university 2020-2023

## **BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE**

Art university of isfahan 2015-2020

#### **DIPLOMA-MATHEMATICS**

SHEIKH ANSARI 2011 - 2015

## RESEARCH INTEREST —

Data-driven method in:

- energy consumption analysis
- daylight
- fire evacuation
- acoustic
- Occupant behavior

## RESEARCH METHODS —

Machine learning (supervisedunsupervised methods)

Structural equation modeling (SEM)

Hypothesis tests

Deep learning methods(CNN-RNN-Gans)

## **SOFTWARES**

python

**Building performance simulation software** 

3d design software

Statistical software

## EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Arman Nikkhah Dehnavi is a data analyst and computer programmer with 7 years of experience in Iran. He has a Master's degree in Building Science and has worked on different research projects that require knowledge in both building science and data science. Moreover, he works as a lecturer in data science for building science in the international building performance simulation association(IBPSA) for 2 years. Also he tries to develop a several web-based software to make building performance evaluations easier.

## EXPERIENCE -

#### LECTURER IN DATA SCIENCE IN BUILDING SCIENCE

IBPSA, Iran, Tehran | 2021 - Presente

#### **RESEARCHE ASSISTANT**

Innovation center of architecture and urban planning- shahid beheshti university. | 2022 – presente

#### **TECHNICAL ASSISTANT**

Innovation center of architecture and urban planning- shahid beheshti university. | 2022 - presente

#### **PYTHON DEVELOPER AND JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST**

BSPsim startup, Iran, Tehran | 2020 - present

## **RESEARCHER AND ARDUINO DEVELOPER**

Fablab fabino , Iran, Isfahan | 2019- 2021

## **CO-FOUNDER AND ARCHITECT**

more office, Iran, Isfahan | 2015-2021

## **PUBLICATIONS**

- Productivity management of construction machinery in large civil engineering projects of Isfahan
  Municipality 13th international progect management conference
- Estimating the Impact of Occupants' Behaviour on Energy Consumption by Pls-SEM: A Case Study
  of Pakdel Residential Complex in Isfahan, IRAN Frontiers in Sustainable Cities
- Application of Machine Learning Methods in the Analysis of Building Emergency Evacuation at Early Design Stages 4th International Conference on Civil Engineering, Architecture, Art and Urban Design
- Feasibility Study for Poverty Alleviation by Energy Production Through Photovoltaic Panels in Underprivileged Areas of Iran (in persian) journal of renewable and new energy
- Compilation of structural components estimation method; Case example: steel and concrete moment frame residential buildings in Tehran (in Persian) The First International Conference on Built Environment in Digital Age
- Early Design Stage Evaluation of Architectural Factors in Fire Emergency Evacuation of the Buildings Using Pix2Pix and Explainable XGBoost Model Journal of Building Performance Simulation
- Targeting modular adaptive façade personalization in a shared office space using fuzzy logic and genetic optimization Journal of Building Engineering